export const quiz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "In which continent Republic of Mauritius is located?",
      choices: ["South America", "Africa", "Asia"],
      correctAnswer: "Africa",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the official language in Guam?",
      choices: ["Spanish", "English", "Chamorro"],
      correctAnswer: "Chamorro",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the capital of Republic of Haiti?",
      choices: ["Port-au-Prince", "Paris", "Beijing"],
      correctAnswer: "Port-au-Prince",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the population in the Republic of Albania?",
      choices: ["2 800 000", "5 400 000", "1 500 000"],
      correctAnswer: "2 800 000",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is Cyprus?",
      choices: ["Asia", "Europe", "Africa"],
      correctAnswer: "Europe",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the currency on Solomon Islands?",
      choices: ["US Dollar", "Australian Dollar", "Solomon Island Dollar"],
      correctAnswer: "Solomon Island Dollar",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the capital of Nepal?",
      choices: ["New Delhi", "Thimphu", "Kathmandu"],
      correctAnswer: "Kathmandu",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the population of the USA?",
      choices: ["330 000 000", "410 000 000", "250 000 000"],
      correctAnswer: "330 000 000",
    },
    {
      question: "Which one is the neighbour of Slovakia?",
      choices: ["Hungary", "Germany", "Slovenia"],
      correctAnswer: "Hungary",
    },
    {
      question: "Where Quatar is located?",
      choices: ["Europe", "Africa", "Asia"],
      correctAnswer: "Asia",
    },
    {
      question: "Where Republic of Mozambique is located?",
      choices: ["Eastern Africa", "Western Africa", "South Africa"],
      correctAnswer: "Eastern Africa",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the capital of Republic of Zimbabwe?",
      choices: ["Maputo", "Gaborone", "Harare"],
      correctAnswer: "Harare",
    },
    {
      question: "What currency is in use in Croatia?",
      choices: ["Korona", "Euro", "Kuna"],
      correctAnswer: "Euro",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the official language in Bosnia and Herzegovina?",
      choices: ["Bosnian", "Serbian", "Albanian"],
      correctAnswer: "Bosnian",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the capital of State of Kuwait?",
      choices: ["Kuwait", "Riyadh", "Kuwait city"],
      correctAnswer: "Kuwait city",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the population of Federative Republic of Brazil",
      choices: ["158 000 000", "213 000 000", "284 000 000"],
      correctAnswer: "213 000 000",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the official language in Co-operative Republic of Guyana?",
      choices: ["English", "Spanish", "Portuguese"],
      correctAnswer: "English",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the official currency in Plurinational State of Bolivia?",
      choices: [
        "Bolivian dollar",
        "United States dollar",
        "Bolivian boliviano",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Bolivian boliviano",
    },
    {
      question: "Where New Zealand is located?",
      choices: ["Oceania", "Asia", "Africa"],
      correctAnswer: "Oceania",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the population of Tuvalu?",
      choices: ["24 000", "16 000", "12 000"],
      correctAnswer: "12 000",
    },
  ],
};
